<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thrity Day</string>
    <string name="day_1">This session focuses on gently introducing your body to movement through light stretching and easy exercises. The goal is to increase blood flow, loosen stiff muscles, and mentally prepare yourself for a consistent fitness routine while reducing the risk of soreness or injury.</string>
    <string name="day_2">Today emphasizes light cardiovascular activity such as walking or slow jogging to improve heart health. Consistent movement helps increase stamina, burn calories, and elevate your mood while keeping the intensity manageable for beginners.</string>
    <string name="day_3">Strength training is introduced using simple bodyweight exercises. Movements like squats, push-ups, and lunges help activate major muscle groups, improve coordination, and begin building a solid strength foundation.</string>
    <string name="day_4">Flexibility becomes the main focus with stretching routines designed to improve joint mobility. These exercises reduce muscle tightness, improve posture, and help your body recover from previous workouts.</string>
    <string name="day_5">Core training takes priority to strengthen abdominal and lower back muscles. A strong core improves balance, stability, and overall movement efficiency, supporting better performance in daily activities and workouts.</string>
    <string name="day_6">This workout combines light cardio with strength exercises to improve endurance and muscle engagement. The balanced routine helps your body adapt to longer activity periods while maintaining proper form.</string>
    <string name="day_7">Active recovery is encouraged through gentle movement, stretching, and deep breathing. This allows muscles to repair while keeping the body active, helping prevent stiffness and maintain flexibility.</string>
    <string name="day_8">Cardio duration increases slightly to challenge endurance and lung capacity. Steady movement trains the heart to work more efficiently while improving overall energy levels throughout the day.</string>
    <string name="day_9">Lower body strength is targeted with exercises that engage the thighs, glutes, and calves. Strong legs improve mobility, balance, and power while supporting joint health.</string>
    <string name="day_10">Upper body exercises focus on arms, shoulders, chest, and back. These movements enhance strength, posture, and functional ability for everyday tasks like lifting and carrying.</string>
    <string name="day_11">Balance and coordination exercises are introduced to improve body control. These movements strengthen stabilizing muscles and reduce the risk of falls or injuries.</string>
    <string name="day_12">A combination of cardio and core exercises boosts calorie burning while strengthening the midsection. This balanced approach improves endurance and supports overall fitness progress.</string>
    <string name="day_13">Attention is placed on posture and controlled movement. Practicing proper alignment improves exercise effectiveness and helps prevent long-term muscle strain.</string>
    <string name="day_14">Recovery and relaxation are emphasized through stretching or light yoga. This helps release tension, calm the mind, and prepare the body for upcoming workouts.</string>
    <string name="day_15">This milestone reinforces consistency and discipline. Reflecting on progress helps build confidence and motivation to continue improving strength and endurance.</string>
    <string name="day_16">Interval training is introduced to elevate heart rate in short bursts. This method improves cardiovascular fitness and increases calorie burn efficiently.</string>
    <string name="day_17">Full-body exercises engage multiple muscle groups simultaneously. This approach improves coordination, strength, and functional fitness.</string>
    <string name="day_18">Breathing techniques are emphasized to enhance oxygen delivery and exercise performance. Controlled breathing improves endurance and relaxation.</string>
    <string name="day_19">Core stability exercises support spinal alignment and overall strength. A stable core enhances balance and reduces lower back strain.</string>
    <string name="day_20">Strength intensity increases slightly with controlled repetitions. This encourages muscle growth while maintaining proper technique.</string>
    <string name="day_21">Light activity and stretching support recovery while maintaining movement consistency. This helps the body recharge without becoming inactive.</string>
    <string name="day_22">Flexibility training improves range of motion and muscle elasticity. Consistent stretching supports long-term mobility and injury prevention.</string>
    <string name="day_23">A blend of cardio and strength training enhances fat burning and endurance. This combination maximizes workout efficiency.</string>
    <string name="day_24">Endurance is challenged through longer workout durations. Sustained movement builds stamina and mental resilience.</string>
    <string name="day_25">Mental focus and motivation are emphasized to strengthen commitment. Developing discipline supports long-term fitness success.</string>
    <string name="day_26">Targeted exercises address weaker muscle areas. Strengthening imbalances improves overall performance and stability.</string>
    <string name="day_27">Balance and coordination challenges improve body awareness. These exercises enhance agility and control.</string>
    <string name="day_28">Recovery techniques such as stretching and relaxation help muscles heal. This prepares the body for final challenges.</string>
    <string name="day_29">Effort and confidence are encouraged while maintaining safety. Pushing limits carefully builds strength and self-belief.</string>
    <string name="day_30">This session celebrates progress and reinforces healthy habits. Continuing regular exercise supports long-term physical and mental well-being.</string>
    <string name="day_1_title">Getting Started</string>
    <string name="day_2_title">Light Cardio</string>
    <string name="day_3_title">Basic Strength</string>
    <string name="day_4_title">Flexibility Training</string>
    <string name="day_5_title">Core Activation</string>
    <string name="day_6_title">Cardio and Strength</string>
    <string name="day_7_title">Active Recovery</string>
    <string name="day_8_title">Building Endurance</string>
    <string name="day_9_title">Lower Body Focus</string>
    <string name="day_10_title">Upper Body Strength</string>
    <string name="day_11_title">Balance and Control</string>
    <string name="day_12_title">Core and Cardio</string>
    <string name="day_13_title">Posture Awareness</string>
    <string name="day_14_title">Stretch and Relax</string>
    <string name="day_15_title">Halfway Progress</string>
    <string name="day_16_title">Interval Training</string>
    <string name="day_17_title">Full Body Workout</string>
    <string name="day_18_title">Breathing Techniques</string>
    <string name="day_19_title">Core Stability</string>
    <string name="day_20_title">Strength Progression</string>
    <string name="day_21_title">Light Movement</string>
    <string name="day_22_title">Improving Flexibility</string>
    <string name="day_23_title">Fat Burning Combo</string>
    <string name="day_24_title">Endurance Challenge</string>
    <string name="day_25_title">Mental Focus</string>
    <string name="day_26_title">Targeted Strength</string>
    <string name="day_27_title">Coordination Training</string>
    <string name="day_28_title">Recovery Session</string>
    <string name="day_29_title">Confidence Boost</string>
    <string name="day_30_title">Fitness Achievement</string>

</resources>